<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30 Tips</string>

    <string name="tip_count">Tip %1$d</string>

    <string name="read_more">Read More</string>
    <string name="collapse">Collapse</string>

    <string name="library_card_title">Get A Library Card</string>
    <string name="new_language_title">Learn A New Language</string>
    <string name="do_a_pullup_title">If You Can\'t Do A Pull-up, You Have A Problem</string>
    <string name="start_investing_title">Start Investing Your Money</string>
    <string name="explore_world_title">Explore The World</string>
    <string name="take_a_walk_title">Take A 10 To 30 Minute Walk Every Day</string>
    <string name="cooking">Learn Cooking</string>
    <string name="acts_of_kindness">Show Random Acts Of Kindness</string>
    <string name="eat_a_breakfast">Have A Big And Healthy Breakfast</string>
    <string name="make_friends">Make Friends</string>
    <string name="get_alone">Get Alone And Practice Solitude</string>
    <string name="help_someone">Help Someone</string>
    <string name="work_on_your_goals">Work On Your Dreams And Goals</string>
    <string name="adopt_pet">Adopt A Pet</string>
    <string name="go_offline">Go Offline</string>
    <string name="get_a_makeover">Get A Makeover</string>
    <string name="do_something_scary">Do Something You\'re Afraid Of Doing</string>
    <string name="surprise_a_loved_one">Surprise A Loved One</string>
    <string name="host_a_party">Host A Party</string>
    <string name="attend_concerts">Attend Concerts</string>
    <string name="master_a_skill">Learn To Master A Skill</string>
    <string name="travel_alone">Travel alone</string>
    <string name="just_relax">Relax And Do Absolutely Nothing</string>
    <string name="block_negative_thoughts">Block Negative Thoughts</string>
    <string name="be_a_minimalist">Be A Minimalist</string>
    <string name="stop_impressing_people">Stop Trying To Impress People</string>
    <string name="make_mistakes">Know it\'s Okay to Make Mistakes</string>
    <string name="avoid_debt">Avoid Debt</string>
    <string name="remember_people">Remember People\'s Names And Birthdays</string>
    <string name="be_grateful">Be Grateful</string>

    <string name="library_card_description">Reading is good for you because it improves your focus, memory, empathy, and communication skills. It can reduce stress, improve your mental health, and help you live longer. Reading also allows you to learn new things to help you succeed in your work and relationships.</string>
    <string name="new_language_description">Besides having more chances of landing a good job or advancing in your career, learning a second language can also give you an insight into other cultures. You will be more prepared and confident to travel the world and explore other people\'s ways of living. Lack of integration is a real problem for most countries.</string>
    <string name="do_a_pullup_description">In addition to working your back, pull-ups strengthen and sculpt your shoulders, forearms, and chest (pecs). When properly performed, they also engage your abs, including your deep transverse abdominis, making them a great exercise for targeting many of the major muscles in the body.</string>
    <string name="start_investing_description">Investing is an effective way to put your money to work and potentially build wealth. Smart investing may allow your money to outpace inflation and increase in value. The greater growth potential of investing is primarily due to the power of compounding and the risk-return tradeoff.</string>
    <string name="explore_world_description">One of the greatest life tips is to explore the world. You don\'t need to be a millionaire to get out there and explore. Some of the best trips can be had for only a couple hundred dollars. You can go on a road trip and explore new cities and states or you fly overseas to experience a different culture. Exploring the world is about exposure to different types of people and living so you can put together as many different perspectives to understand what life\'s all about. </string>
    <string name="take_a_walk_description">Something as simple as a daily brisk walk can help you live a healthier life. For example, regular brisk walking can help you: Maintain a healthy weight and lose body fat. Prevent or manage various conditions, including heart disease, stroke, high blood pressure, cancer and type 2 diabetes.</string>
    <string name="cooking_description">Learning to cook will help you understand world cultures, customs and flavors. You will also learn life skills like eating healthy, budgeting your money, and cleaning. Save some cash. Cooking is less expensive than eating at restaurants, fast food joints and school cafeterias.</string>
    <string name="acts_of_kindness_description">It wouldn\'t hurt to perform random acts of kindness. In fact, it would bring joy to other people, and you would realize you can really make a difference. Offer a seat for the elderly. Pay for someone\'s bus fare. Treat a random person to dinner. Assist someone carrying too many things. You may not become the type of hero portrayed in movies, but you can surely help someone in your own little ways.</string>
    <string name="eat_a_breakfast_description">Breakfast is often called "the most important meal of the day", and for good reason. As the name suggests, breakfast breaks the overnight fasting period. It replenishes your supply of glucose to boost your energy levels and alertness, while also providing other essential nutrients required for good health.</string>
    <string name="make_friends_description">Friends prevent isolation and loneliness and give you a chance to offer needed companionship, too. Friends can also: Increase your sense of belonging and purpose. Boost your happiness and reduce your stress.</string>
    <string name="get_alone_description">One of the greatest benefits of spending time alone is how it helps you develop a better understanding of who you are. The more you know and understand yourself the more likely you are to do things that you love, learn things that interest you and spend time with people who make you feel good.</string>
    <string name="help_someone_description">Helping others is thought to be one of the ways that people create, maintain, and strengthen their social connections. For example, volunteering and helping others can help us feel a sense of belonging, make new friends, and connect with our communities.</string>
    <string name="work_on_your_goals_description">You can never move forward without taking action on your dreams. Living your dream is exciting and fun. There\'s no way you can live an interesting life without living your dreams. So commit to taking action and work on what you want to achieve in your life. These are the fuels and the drive that will show you how you should live an exciting life.</string>
    <string name="adopt_pet_description">Adopting a pet comes with responsibilities, but doesn\'t that make your life more interesting and exciting? After a tiring day at work, you have a cute and lovable cat or puppy waiting for you to come home. You will always look forward to playing with your pet/s.</string>
    <string name="go_offline_description">Who isn\'t guilty of checking on his or her phone right after waking up? Who doesn\'t browse his or her Facebook, Twitter, or Instagram account for a couple of hours every day? Instead of looking at how people are doing with their lives, why don\'t you disconnect from the online world sometimes? Make use of that time to talk to your family and friends. Make use of the time to be one with nature. Make use of the time to plan for your next adventure.</string>
    <string name="get_a_makeover_description">Been wanting to get a pixie cut? Why don\'t you do it now? Get a new haircut. Try a different makeup. Buy a new dress. Change your style. You will look fresh. You will feel more confident. Watch Youtube videos, and do the makeover by yourself. Or, do it with your best friend. The makeover might be a disaster, but that\'s what makes it more fun.</string>
    <string name="do_something_scary_description">Afraid of heights? Afraid of leaving your boring job? Afraid of changes? Why don\'t you face your fears one step at a time? Try extreme sports. Go bungee jumping or mountain climbing. Quit your job. Of course, you need to save up first before doing that. However, the idea is for you to embrace changes. Life will be more interesting and exciting if you are open to changes.</string>
    <string name="surprise_a_loved_one_description">Sometimes, you get too focused on the idea that life is so boring that you tend to ignore the people around you. Remember that there are so many people who love you. They are always there for you. Why don\'t you show them how much you appreciate them? Give your dear mother a surprise. Treat your significant other to a date or a  surprise weekend getaway. Send flowers. Express your love for them.</string>
    <string name="host_a_party_description">Sick and tired of staying at home all by yourself? Why don\'t you invite your friends over for dinner? Host a party. Sing your heart out. Dance with your friends. Play some games. Goofing around with your friends will surely lift up your spirit.</string>
    <string name="attend_concerts_description">You\'ve been working hard to earn a living. You deserve to have fun and enjoy life, so why don\'t you get a ticket to your favorite artist or band? Don\'t miss the concert. Invite your special someone or your friends, and enjoy a night full of love and music.</string>
    <string name="master_a_skill_description">What one skill that you have always wanted to learn but never does? It is time for you to master that skill and become the best in it. It can be managing your business, playing golf, swimming, singing, playing guitar, etc. Mastering something and becoming the best in it will make your life fulfilling. You will feel worth it and extremely satisfied when you do.</string>
    <string name="travel_alone_description">Have you tried to travel alone? You should try it. There\'s no need for you to travel overseas or to a foreign country yourself right away. You can always start small. Probably you can go for a one-day trip alone and see how you like it. And then you can grow bigger from there. When you think about traveling alone to countries that you have never been to before, it will make you thrill and excited.</string>
    <string name="just_relax_description">Imagine lying on the beach while enjoying the sunset and doing nothing, how nice is that? If you can\'t get to the beach, you can sit on your balcony; enjoy the great view with your favorite beverage. You should enjoy life more. Sometimes you will get stuck and feel like going nowhere in life. So slow down and relax. Enjoy the moment and do absolutely nothing. You will be surprise how this can make you more productive and make your life interesting.</string>
    <string name="block_negative_thoughts_description">If you\'re looking to live a good life, a life tip to consider is blocking negative thoughts. Yeah, I know, way easier said than done. You\'re going to be telling your brain to quiet down a million times those first few weeks. But there is a way to reduce negative thoughts. You need to learn how to replace negative thoughts with happy thoughts. When a toxic thought enters your mind, you\'ll need to think of a new positive thought to replace it. Don\'t let that Negative Nancy in your head spiral you down the path of no return.</string>
    <string name="be_a_minimalist_description">Being a minimalist can save you from so many headaches. If you live in a small home with not a lot of stuff, that can actually be a good thing. There\'s less to clean and less to worry about. Things don\'t give life meaning. People do. So instead of hoarding junk from the good old days, you might feel relieved to have fewer things than you did before. It feels good to have less stuff.</string>
    <string name="stop_impressing_people_description">Life\'s too short to impress people. In our world, we\'re the most important person. It\'s our responsibility to believe in our importance to keep ourselves alive long enough to reproduce and fulfill our life\'s purpose, at least that\'s what evolution is about. But outside of our world, each person also believes they\'re the most important person. Evolution designed us that way so that we continue to multiply. You\'re never going to convince someone that you\'re more important than they are. No matter how hard you try. Instead, focus on being happy and more stress-free. Live the life you want to live instead of the life others want you to live. Or that you think others want you to live.</string>
    <string name="make_mistakes_description">Just move forward in the right direction. Your happiness will come from learning from the bad decisions you\'ve made. No point in wallowing or spiralling into a negativity vortex to prove you care about your wrongdoings. Laugh off your mistakes if it makes sense, apologize to the friend you\'ve hurt, take the advice you always ignore, and challenge yourself to do better next time. You don\'t need to make an example of yourself or turn yourself into a villain. Your past doesn\'t need to haunt you, so make good decisions in the present, so you can have a better future.</string>
    <string name="avoid_debt_description">Debt is so ingrained in so many cultures that most people assume that it\'s impossible to live debt free in the world. While financial hardships can set us off course, we should work hard to avoid being indebted to others. The easiest way to do this is to avoid buying things you don\'t need to impress people. Most people try to one up their friends and family by going bigger. They\'ll buy bigger houses, more cars, and expensive things to appear rich. However, appearing rich and being rich aren\'t the same thing. So, the life tip to follow here is to avoid debt caused by keeping up appearances.</string>
    <string name="remember_people_description">One of the keys to success in life is remembering people\'s names and birthdays. There\'s nothing sweeter than the sound of your name. And when someone remembers your name and birthday it makes you feel special. If you want to live a happy life, go out of your way to celebrate people\'s birthdays. A quick message will make them feel excited on their special day. Do it a day late and the excitement wears off. When you meet someone ask for their name and birthday. Put it on your phone so you don\'t forget. Or repeat their name multiple times as you speak with them, so it doesn\'t slip your mind.</string>
    <string name="be_grateful_description">In life, you\'ll experience many hardships and setbacks. That\'s true. We won\'t deny that. But there are so many people out there who\'ve helped you throughout your life. There have been teachers who\'ve educated you. There have been friends who\'ve stood by your side. You\'ve been given opportunities and things that others might have wanted but never had the chance to get. Each day write down a few things you\'re grateful for and reap the benefits of gratitude. Be mindful of all the things you have instead of all the things you don\'t have. By being mindful of what you have, you begin to appreciate your life in this moment. That way, when you lose some of the things you have now, you\'ll know that you cherished loved ones while you had them in your life.</string>
</resources>
